intokenya.com 2012-12-22

# Privacy Policy

**Security policy**  
Central Reservations Bureau regards the privacy and security of our customer's information as an important component of the service that we offer. When you make a reservation we offer the use of a secure server. The Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology encrypts all information you input before it is sent to our server and when it is sent from our server to the hotel. . 

**What information this site gathers/tracks about you**  
When you make a reservation you will be asked to provide information such as name, contract details and credit card information. You also have the option to join Central Reservations Bureau.com where you can choose to store your contact information and hotel, currency and destination preferences. At any time, you may update your preferences and contact information. 

**What this site does with the information it gathers/tracks**  
For some hotels your credit card details are taken as a guarantee of reservation and Central Reservations Bureau will charge a $4.95 non-refundable service fee to your credit card at the time of booking. For other hotels you pay us via your credit card at time of booking and there is no service charge. Look for information under the heading Payment Method to determine when payment is made. If it says "Guarantee Only" payment is made at the hotel on departure.  
As for optional membership, the information that you provide makes booking on Central Reservations Bureau.com easier for you: contact information allows your booking form to be completed automatically; hotel preferences allow you to match hotels with your specific requirements; currency preferences will display hotel rates in the currency of your choice; destination preferences will default the location used for your availability searches.   
**  
Email a friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We do not store this information. The emails are for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

**With whom this site shares the information it gathers/tracks**  
Central Reservations Bureau forwards your reservation information including (in some cases) payment details to the hotel via a secure connection. We also share aggregate statistics about our customer's traffic patterns and reservations with our suppliers and partners, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information. 

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to remember what you've done since arriving on our site. In technical jargon, cookies allow us to create a "session" for you that helps us remember information such as what hotel, room and rate you've selected so we can book that for you if and when you press the book button. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer's hard disk and echoed back to us when you access our site. They're standard industry practice and many web sites, including ours, will not work well without them. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies but if you prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies.  
The ads appearing on this web site are delivered to users by Real Media Ltd, our Web advertising partner. Information about users' visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. 

**Third party disclosure**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site, or as required by law.  
When the ownership of Central Reservations Bureau changes hands customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the web site. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy. 

**How to Contact Us**  
Central Reservations Bureau is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or would like more information about our company, please
